My name is Frank Frazier, aka Bounty
Tank. I've been a bounty hunter for over
12 years. I have recovered over $1
million in bonds. This is everything I'm
authorized to tell you.
I was on a hunt looking for a guy. This
truck pulled up to me and they was like,
"Hey, you better get off this block."
And they started shooting. I'm running
for my life. There's no one to help you.
It had to be at least 20 shots. So, that
was my first a rude awakening that this
badge don't mean nothing to certain
people.
A bounty hunter is
a agent that goes out to apprehend
fugitives that are on bail that have
skipped court. The misconception people
have for bounty hunting is that it's all
glitz and glamour. People watch it on TV
and all they see is the fun part. They
see that the door kicking, the chasing,
the hunt. They don't see the countless
hours that you're sitting in a car doing
surveillance. They don't see the
the the the death threats you're getting
for looking for certain individuals. You
got people calling, "Threaten you, if
you come back to my house, I'mma kill
you." I have made over now only up
over 2,000 arrests. One of the things
that make me unique is the lengths I'm
willing to go
to find people. I'm very crafty. There
was a young lady, she was a prostitute
and she was on the run. So, what I did
was I put up a Craigslist ad um
advertising that I was shooting a porno.
So, I put the ad up because I was told
that she periodically goes online to
Craigslist and other websites to look
for odd jobs and she wind up hitting
this ad. Probably about a week later we
got a call. She sent photos and she bit.
She bit on it. We gave her a location at
the motel to meet there. We told her
what to expect. We had music playing. We
had the camera set up. Um obviously so
she would think it was a you know
shooting an actual porn.
Um but it was no different because if I
was hunting I would have my camera set
up. So it worked out perfectly. I had my
shirt off. I was well lathered up to
play the part. When she came in she felt
comfortable. Then I told her hey we're
going to switch to this scene. I'm going
to put some handcuffs on you. Things
might get a little wild. And she was
like oh okay I like this. This is a this
is starting to turn out great how I
wanted it to. At this point she's cuffed
up. Then I say okay we're going to go to
the next scene. I'm going to take you to
the car. And she still just going along
with it at this point. I take her to the
car
and she's still not aware what's going
on at this time. We start getting closer
to the police station. Now she's like
where we going? I'm like I'm taking you
to jail.
And she's like
we're we having a scene in jail? I said
you're going to have a scene in jail but
I'm taking you to jail. I'm your bail
bondsman. A bail bondsman is a insurance
agent that loans out money to defendants
who can't necessarily afford to bail out
themselves. Um she realized that the gig
is up. She realized she was going to
jail. So it was crazy. I'm not going to
lie.
You have to be honest with yourself.
Certain places are more friendlier than
others. Earlier on in my years I went to
Detroit. I was on a hunt looking for a
guy.
And I thought that me having a badge
and a gun meant something.
I was around in neighborhood. I was like
on 6 7 mile. Like I was in the trenches.
Handing out
uh uh this was old so I was handing out
pictures, flyers. Have you seen this
guy? Seen this guy? Walking around just
willy-nilly. And I'll never forget this
truck pulled up to me and they was like,
"Hey,
you better get off this block.
Get out of here. If we come back here
and you still here,
it's going to be problems." Paying no
attention. Again, I'm high and mighty.
I'm thinking, "Whatever, they're not
going to do nothing to me. They're just
talking."
They came back.
Maybe about an hour or so
and they started shooting and chasing
me. And I'll never forget, I remember
finally getting to this abandoned
building and I was hiding
and they were still looking. So, walking
around looking, looking, looking.
I had dropped my phone and I'm on the
call. I was just sitting in there
scared out of my life thinking, "Wow,
this this is is about to be over." So,
I'm sitting in there and they stayed out
there looking for for for at least about
45 minutes. And I waited at least
another hour 15 minutes before I left.
Don't ever get it twisted to think that
I'm above or
um I can do anything I want or talk to
anybody
any type of way because there's people
who don't care about that and they'll
put you in your place. I've been out at
the mall several times with my family. I
was out with my wife, my daughter. I see
a guy that has a warrant.
I've been looking for him for a while.
He sees me, I see him.
And at this point, I'm like, "I can't do
this here. My kid's here. My wife is
here. This could literally go south." In
those situations,
you got to pick and choose, you know, is
is are you going to prioritize your job
or your family at that point? And this
has happened to me multiple times where
we get to a person's house or in their
neighborhood, in their hood, and they
have 30 guys with them, armed to the
teeth, and police won't come out and
help us.
What do you do at that point?
You let your ego, your pride get in
in front of you? No.
You got to understand that if you
approach this situation with the ego,
that you may not
As far as tracking, my first method that
I'm always going to do
is go straight to social media. I'm
going to see you posting stuff on
Facebook or Instagram or you're live. If
I don't
find any social media, I'm going to
start looking, finding out where you
hang out at. He lives here. Let me go
check with this store. Does this guy
come in here? Yeah, he comes here every
day gets and gets a pack of cigarettes.
So, you start you learn their habits.
Then it goes to association. 95% of the
time, I'm not even hunting these guys.
I'm looking for the women that they hang
with because they're not hiding.
And they're always going to post them
online. I'm here so-and-so and you might
see his foot in the background. So,
early on in my career,
um
I
was good at my job. So, I would catch
someone
and other bondsmen would recommend me to
other bondsmen.
And this particular lady reached out to
me, this particular bondsman, and she,
um
said, "Hey, I'm looking for this guy. I
I got him off a million dollars. I
cannot find him." So, if I found this
guy with this million-dollar bond,
I would make 10% of that, which is
$100,000. So, that's a lot of money.
This was like a major payday for me. I
was struggling at the time just trying
to
make a career out of this. She gave me
this case file. I looked into it. I
figured this particular guy, he was a he
was a street guy. He sold drugs. He had
several women, but I found one
particular woman that he had a kid with.
Um so, I knew he would
he was an active father as much as he
could being in the streets. So, I knew
that he was at some point he would come
back to visit her to see his son. And
she was a dancer, so there was no
loyalty. She was going to go whoever had
the money. So, when I found out where
she danced, I started to frequently go
in there.
I would purposely
request her. I would purposely spend
money on her
to the point where she got a little
comfortable. How was so-and-so? Hey, how
you doing? Again, I wouldn't do this
today. I'm married.
But, um we started to
develop a relationship. I can't remember
exactly what I told her I did for a
living. I just told her I get money. And
that was cool with her. I probably put
in
thousands of dollars to find this person
to to you know to court her, take her
out. So, after about a month of courting
her, kicking it, spending some money, we
finally got to a day it was Father's
Day.
And she was like, "Yeah, hey, he's going
to come pick up um her son at this
time." So, I'm like, "Cool." So, this
day I had made sure I had my vest
packed up in my bag and all my
tools that I needed. I never forget he
knocked on the door, he came in. I
started thinking like, man, this is kind
of messed up. You kind of start feeling
bad a little bit, you know? So, I'm
like,
"Woo! Okay." So, I go put my stuff on.
I come out.
He's sitting at the table, so he has
nowhere to go. I come out and they just
kind of looking at me like,
and I'm like, "Hey, bro, you know, I
hate to do this, man, but you know,
you're under arrest. You got a warrant
for your arrest. I'm your bondsman." So,
he immediately starts going off on her
thinking that she set him up.
Going off, getting belligerent. I wind
up getting him in control,
talking to him real calm like, "This is
what it is." He wind up just being
compliant, putting his hands behind his
back. Now,
you would think the trouble would come
from him. Oh, no.
The trouble came from her. She started
to commence a ass whooping on me.
Swinging, kicking, spitting on me. She
was just
and I understand it. I understand. I
understand. She was just She felt
betrayed. She was just confused. She was
angry. And I felt bad about it. So, I
was like, I I can never do that again
even I don't care how much the money's
worth.
As a bondsman, we try to stay away from
gang members if all possible. Sometimes
you don't know they're affiliated with a
gang and it just is what it is. But we
deal with all type of cases from
misdemeanors to F1 felonies. There was a
situation
where I bonded out a guy. He was uh
trafficking marijuana, truckloads,
semis.
And we got him out for uh trafficking
drugs. I remember going to this guy's
house,
knocking on the door like, "Hey, uh you
got a payment coming up. I need you to
make sure you get a payment." And he
looked at me through my soul.
Um there's not too many guys that just
look at me and just
look at me like I'm nothing. Like I just
seen his eyes,
he was different. He wasn't a normal
fugitive that we go after. Turns out he
was a part of the cartel. Now,
at this moment, when I found this out, I
said, "Oh my god, hope this guy goes to
court."
We don't want to be searching for a
cartel member. And God,
sense of humor,
he missed court.
So,
at this point, I am I'm not afraid to go
after anyone.
This is a job, this is what comes with
it. You got to do what you got to do or
you lose money. But at this point, I'm
like,
Shh.
I mean, how do we how are we going to do
this? We can't lose the money, but then
again,
we can't put our family and our life on
jeopardy looking for this guy. But
luckily for us,
it went federal and the feds picked it
up and we didn't have to go after him.
That was a situation where
I don't know what would have happened,
to be honest with you. There was another
situation and me and Tony that's who I
work with now, where we walked up to a
house, we were just doing something
normal, going to knock on the door just
to have a conversation. We're about to
go knock on the door and the guy we
wanted to talk to literally hops out the
bushes and comes around us.
And he could have just shot. He could
have He could have took us down. So, he
seen us on the cameras and was in the
bushes, not knowing who we were until we
kind of got up. He kind of seen, you
know, identification and badges. But, it
could have went bad again. You just have
situations like this. It's a dangerous
job. You start to get a little
desensitized to things. We I remember we
went to this guy's house. He was He was
a older guy. And he literally had a
pistol on him. And me and Antonio just
kind of sitting there, "Hey, put put the
pistol down." Like, just super calm.
And retrospect, looking hindsight, we're
like, "Man, this guy could have shot
us." And looking back at it kind of
shook me a little bit because sometimes
we're so desensitized to things that um
you don't really realize it.
We get the word that the individual is
in a certain location. We're going to go
surveillance the house first. The
longest I've had to stay in a car was 3
days. I got intel
from someone saying, "Hey, he's in the
house for sure."
But, it was a third-party house, so I
couldn't just go barge into this house
legally without physically seeing him.
So, if it's a third-party house, it's
not on the application or the warrant,
um you can't just go in there unless you
see them. If you physically identify
them in this house, we have the legal
right to go in there. So, I knew this
guy was in this house.
I knew if I left it was a possibility
that he would leave. And I was just
waiting for one sign for him to pop his
head out. And I also knew
that he probably knew
that I was sitting outside.
So, at this point, it's it's a waiting
game. Who's going to out-wait who?
And he might have thought that since I
was in the car that eventually I would
leave. He didn't know.
I stayed in that car. I had jugs of
urine in there. You know, that you got
to pee in a bottle.
I DoorDash food. I ordered a pizza, sat
up there, ate.
I literally stayed there for 3 days.
And finally, like I said, at some point
he popped his head out. At that point, I
called everybody and said, "Hey, I just
seen him. It's go time." But if I didn't
have the patience to sit there for those
3 days and thug it out, I would have
probably knocked on the door and burned
the address.
Now you're back at
level one. Yeah.
So, we're going to see how many points
of entry, windows. We're going to assess
the entire situation. We're going to
find out how many people are in the
house, is this individual armed, what
does this individual have on. Once we
get all this information that we'll
combine as a team, we'll collab, we'll
meet somewhere maybe a mile away from
the house. You don't want to meet too
close just in case someone's driving by
and they see us, obviously. And
nowadays, a lot of people have cameras,
so they can see you coming. They can,
you know, be prepared for you. Also,
we're going to contact local law
enforcement to let them know, "Hey, it's
Frank Frazier. I'm in the area. I'm a
bail bondsman. We're about to try to
apprehend so-and-so where this address.
We are armed. There's X amount of guys."
So, they know exactly what's going on
cuz a lot of times um when you're about
to go hunt, people might see a bunch of
guys putting on gear, and then they call
the police. And then the cops show up
and they don't know what's going on.
They're going to draw their guns or draw
and now you got a whole situation. That
is the process before we even get to
getting to the house. Um then we want to
make sure everyone's getting dressed,
you know, we're getting a bulletproof
vest, we're going to have handcuffs.
Definitely want to have mace. Um and and
a and a taser. And someone's always
going to have a gun. The only time it
may switch up is if we have to breach a
house. And we need a sledgehammer or a
battering ram. Um body cameras on. You
want to make sure you it's getting
documented because a lot of times things
can happen and people may lie on you.
You know, you want to make sure that you
are holding yourself accountable and
also that you have something to cover
your ass if something does go wrong. Me
personally, I think the most important
quality of being a bounty hunter would
be
you have to
embed patience.
If you don't have patience, you're going
to suck at this. A lot of
guys in today's hunting industry,
they're more smash and grab. They leave
with the hammer.
There's no finesse. Instead of sitting
on this house and watching it for 10
days first,
they go burn the address.
The address is burned. He's never going
to come back there.
Under federal law,
we are legally permitted to
pursue a fugitive in any dwelling. It's
a law that's called Taylor versus
Tainter. We sometimes bump heads with
law enforcement because they don't know
our laws and they're like, you need a
warrant to do that. We can't do that,
but
we abide by different laws. It's
different laws. It's bail laws. If the
cosigner signs this bail contract
and we're in agreement
and
this person is hiding in your house, we
can break entry if we need to. You know,
we're going to knock first, but if we
need to come in and kick the door and
breach it, we have every legal right to.
This was a case I had in Youngstown,
Ohio. There was a situation with a guy
his girlfriend. I was looking for this
young lady a while. This was a $75,000
bond as well. This individual, we had to
track him all the way down
to third-party house
and I found out that he's staying there.
He's renting there. His name's on the
lease. I got word
that she was there. He didn't think that
I can come into this house, which he had
a rude awakening. And he was like, "You
can't come in here. I didn't put this on
application." After about 5 minutes, he
said, "Fine, come in and check."
So, I checked upstairs. She's obviously
not upstairs hiding. So, now there's a
door leading downstairs that is
conveniently locked.
So, I said, "Hey, man, open this door."
"I can't open this door. This is not my
house.
You can't go in here." So, now he's
chest to now trying to get bold like,
"You ain't doing nothing." So, now I
know
she's in there hiding. Because if she
wasn't, he wouldn't be putting this much
of a fight up. So, I know exactly when
someone is lying to me. 90% of the time
when I'm asking questions,
I already know the answer to. I just
want to see what you're going to say. At
this point, I started to kick this door
in to go downstairs. Once we go
downstairs, I get to searching. What do
you know? She's underneath the bed
hiding. He comes downstairs, tries to
get loud and bug. You know, I I say,
"Hey, you know, I can take this off and
we can handle this as men and we can get
back to this." And he kindly declined.
Most of them do decline. So,
again, I'm not a police officer. Is this
the most professional thing to do? No.
Um but sometimes
it calls for it. I don't do that these
days, but yeah, earlier in my days,
yeah, I was a little bit more,
you know,
wild.
When you have a contract with a
bondsman, my standard is 10%. Again,
I've been doing this for a while. So,
when you hire me,
I'm I want the full amount. I would say
mostly like
5 to 50,000 is the typical. But the
higher it is, the more tighter usually
bondsmen are, so you don't get as many
as those. That million dollar one is the
is the biggest one I've ever collected.
So, back, this was some years ago, we
had to look for a guy named Ted Palmer.
He was known as a meth cooker, and he
eventually was convicted of drug
trafficking. The bond was $75,000.
It took me 6 months. Not only was I
looking for him, local police was
looking for him. This guy was different.
He could live anywhere. No one wanted to
give us answers, and you know, we had X
amount of days to find him. And we got
down to the last day before we had to
pay out the $75,000. The last possible
day, I wound up going to Ted's
friend's house,
um who knew where he was. And he drew up
a map where Ted was. I called up the
task force. I said, "Hey, I got word
about where this guy is. I think it's
the real deal this time." Once the task
force got there, we all got suited up.
My adrenaline is is is is pumping. It
was me, the task force, went into the
trailer, drew him out. They put on the
cuffs, cuffed him up, had no clue that
we were ever going to find him, but that
was it. After that, he was caught. But
it got down to literally the last day
where they said, "You either find him,
or you got to cough up that $75,000."
So,
um thanking God we found him that day.
There's obviously drug epidemic going on
now. I mean, it hasn't stopped.
The worse it gets with drugs, the more
skips we get. There was one year where
all I was looking for was was drug
addicts. And
it's because they
they fear withdrawals more than they
fear me.
Because they get sick. It's a horrible
experience
when you're taking drugs every day, and
then you just go cold turkey, and you
got to sit in jail. And they fear that,
so they'll take off and run.
And they're more afraid of going through
that than actually
getting arrested by me. So, yeah, with
the drugs, there's more skips. And it
might be a situation where you don't
find a person for a month. You don't
catch them, you don't eat. When you're
hunting, you're gone all the time. It's
hard to
to to to maintain a
a stable household cuz you're always
going hunting. And you're just trying to
find that next book, that next book. You
just you're literally chasing money.
Literally, you're chasing money. So, in
Ohio,
if you just want to hunt and make a
living off of it, you're not going to
make a living.
It's not enough to go around. Honestly,
you need to be a bondsman. I would
recommend doing both
to to get the full benefit of the
industry. Yeah.
Me personally, I started in Virginia and
I got a bounty hunter license in
Virginia and I went through a company at
the time. I don't think they're they're
no longer around, but I went through a
company and they specifically trained
for this specific job. So, you learn
like handcuffing, clearing houses, just
different tactical work. So, that was my
base of it. Now, they didn't teach you
the skills you need to know when you're
out really dealing with people. You just
have to have some type of street
awareness. If you don't have good
instinct, you're not going to do well.
So, typically guys who are from
certain areas, they know I shouldn't go
over here. I shouldn't approach this
person. White hunter Caucasian hunters
that they can't go in the hood. They
stick out like a sore thumb.
And as soon as they pop up or they seen
in the car sitting doing surveillance,
they're going to be noticed. What made
me really good as I'm young, I'm urban.
I would blend in the neighborhood, so I
could do certain things that other
individuals couldn't do. Now, there's
situations where I go into environments
where there's no black people around.
Some of the cops are kind of old school,
a little racist. I'm going to take
someone with the with the a friendlier
skin color with me. This particular case
was early on in my years and I went to a
specific bondsman, and I was like, "Hey,
you got some work?" He was like, "Not
really." He was like, "But I do got one
guy that I'm having a hard time
finding." And it was one of them
situations where he's a white guy,
and he can't go in the hood. He's not
afraid to go in there. He'll do what
he's got to do.
But he just couldn't cuz he stuck out,
and everyone knew him. So, he showed me
the guy.
He showed me where the one of his uh
kids' moms was staying. So, what I did
was
I went to his uh girlfriend's house,
asked to get my hair braided. And I
called him. I was like, "Hey, uh he's in
here." So, he came, rushed, we arrested
dude. You just have to have some type of
street awareness. So, my first hunting
experience actually was in It was in
Virginia.
Crazy, I was still in college. I was in
my senior college. I knew I wanted to do
this. I called around
to every bondsman I could. But I never
forget this guy. His name was Michael
Jackson. No lie. And he had this case.
It was a thousand-dollar bond, which you
only get a hundred bucks. But he said,
"Hey, I can't find this guy. I don't
know where he's at.
I heard he's in a hotel somewhere.
That's all I know."
I went in the area to every hotel, and
it had to be about 40-plus hotels. "Hey,
you seen this guy? Hey, you seen this
guy?"
All night. And probably when I got to
about maybe the 30th hotel, they said,
"Yeah, he's in the room so-and-so." I
said, "Ha! It's time. Okay." I said,
"Hey, can I get the key?"
They said, "No." I said, "Well, I'm
going to kick it in."
"Here's the key, sir."
I'll never forget that. My stomach was
bubbling. I was like,
"Am I really doing this?" I'm like,
"Just It's Just remember what you was
taught." So, I started banging on the
door. I said, "Hey, come Come to the
door. It's the It's the Bill Bondsman.
Open up the door." He wouldn't open it.
I said, "Okay."
Open the door.
Um I'll never forget the scene. Bro had
his laptop up.
He had
a Snickers, a grapefruit, and he had
some porn playing
on his computer. And he was butt naked.
It was the oddest setup I've ever seen.
I was like, "Get on the ground.
Put your hands behind your back." I was
like,
"No, no, no, no, no.
Put some clothes on. Put your hands
behind your back." But uh yeah, that was
my first time catching somebody. Yeah,
man. It was It was a wild time, man. But
it It was funny.
When I took him to the jail, I felt
accomplished. I'mma call
call him Michael Jackson. I got him. He
couldn't believe it. He's like, "What?"
Gang gave me my 100 bucks, man. It was
It was uphill since then. Yeah. I spent
more money looking for this guy than I
did getting 100 bucks. I would tell
anybody that's getting into bounty
hunting or law enforcement, period.
If you were bullied as a child as an
adult, and you're trying to use this to
get some type of leverage, don't get
into this.
If you have anger issues,
don't get into this. If you just want to
be able to hold a gun and give commands
and have authority,
don't get into this.
You have to understand that you have a
very big impact on people's lives.
You have to know your laws. And you got
to know how to move with integrity. So,
you got to know what you can and cannot
do. I mean, sometimes you get those guys
who think they're cops.
Um and they start doing too much, and
then they wind up in some trouble, you
know what I mean? So, you got to know
what your lane is.
When someone misses uh court, the court
will notify you. They'll send a
certified letter
um you know, to the office saying, "Hey,
this person missed court. You got x
amount of days. There is
instances where hunters have arrested
the wrong defendant, and
that, because we're not cops, is very
detrimental. Because at that point, it's
kidnapping.
So, you have to be very sure
who you are arresting. You want to check
That's why we get these applications to
check body marks, tattoos,
um so that doesn't happen. So, as a
bounty hunter, who I'm going to
prioritize
who to go and hunt, is two of There's
two factors. How easy it is to find you,
and how much it is.
So, I'm going to weigh both of those.
If you're a very hard person to find,
and
the bond's very high, I might put you to
the side,
and get the easy ones out the way real
quick, and then come to you. And just
that way, I can just focus on this one.
And there's another guy, we called him
Red Dot, and that took me
forever [snorts] to find this guy. There
were probably about three times that we
almost caught him, and he got away. One,
there was a car chase. Now, we're not
allowed to get in high-speed chases, cuz
we're not the police. So, I just let him
go. We almost had him boxed in, he hit
the car, hit my car, bounced got on the
freeway.
Got away. Um
when you're trying to wrestle someone in
the car, it can get dangerous.
You don't want damages to your car, or
his car, and you don't want anyone to
get hurt. So, a lot of times, we just
let them go. Again, we're not police.
So, if it's a situation where
this guy is super dangerous,
we'll get as many people as we need. You
know, if we need 10 people, we're going
to call 10 people up. But usually, it's
about three of us. Simple is safe. But
if we need more, best believe we can get
more. There's multiple reasons why
people run.
You have those that are scared, who's
never really been in the system. They're
going to take off running. You have
those who want to get their
finances
in a better situation. They want to get
more money for a lawyer, so they're all
hustling, trying to work, gather money,
rather than go turn themselves in. Then
you have those who are just
um
on drugs, addicts, and their reality is
different. Some were high, some were
they're not paying attention what's
going on in the world. But those are
really the basic three type of people
who would miss court. The percentage of
people skipping is just varies.
Um when you start getting around holiday
seasons, summertime,
people don't want to go to court. Some
months,
no one skips. You might have a dry
period of
4 months and everyone's just going to
court. Then you have that month where
it's it's all hell and no one's going.
It's a job that you
can't not take home. When you go home,
your phone's still ringing. You're
dealing
every day
with negativity.
And it's taxing on you mentally.
No sleep. You might be away from your
home, from your from your wife, from
your kids. If you don't find a positive
coping mechanism, you can quickly
start using substances
to cope with the stress to numb it.
I started personally
coping with the wrong things. I started
coping with alcohol, just to numb it
sometimes. I started coping with weed,
coping with going to the strip club,
just coping it all with bad mechanisms
that took a toll on my life, personally,
morally, spiritually,
um and ruined my relationship
with, you know, now my ex-wife, you
know, I ruined that relationship. I was
neglecting my daughter
with work and then after work I would go
out and just
indulge in foolery consistently.
Um where it started the chaos started to
really uh it started to become part of
my life and I started really losing
myself
um just with the stress of it. And then,
you know, I started
to deal with my own personal demons. I
started to fall victim to just just
dealing with women and the drugs and the
and alcohol and it it tore me to pieces
and I knew I needed to get right, but I
just kept pushing it pushing it.
October 10th,
2024, the day I'll never forget.
It's the day I was shot. Simple case, it
wasn't nothing
out the ordinary. We got a call like,
"Hey, he's here." It was like, "All
right, let's go out. We already in
Akron." So,
just a normal day. So, we get to the
house.
The the young lady's feeding me
information. He's here. He's here. I'm
like, "Well, get him to come outside."
We were circling around the house for
probably about 20 minutes. Listening,
scoping out, seeing, you know, what's
going on. Normal tactic that I do. She
finally called, she said, "He's outside
on the porch. Hurry up." So, I hear him
go on the porch.
I then run
to the back. I scream, "Hands."
And then he shoots twice. My life
flashed in front of my front of my eyes.
I remember
feeling myself like, "Did he get me?"
I'm like, "I hope he got my vest."
And I took my vest off and I I felt the
blood. I was like, "Oh."
The way I was running,
it shot the side of it right here. Just
missed my heart by 2 cm. I was still
talking. I was moving. You know, at the
time the guy I was with, I told him to
call the police, call the ambulance.
Had him apply pressure where he could.
And police picked me up, put me in the
ambulance, and uh
it was a blur after that. It was a blur,
man. Um the doctors said I was a
miracle.
They said they don't know how I made it.
They had me on something called
methylene blue.
And it's it's literally it's blue. They
give it to you to to keep your blood
pressure up. Um
cuz I had flatlined also. They said that
uh when usually a patient gets methylene
blue,
they're at their end, and they don't
they rarely see people recover
who have to receive this. They said they
seen two out of their time ever being
there. My life changed
um
completely after that. But for the
better. I spent 6 months in the
hospital.
I had to relearn how to walk,
eat. I lost my really my identity. I
went to went through like a identity
crisis. I was always known for my big
stature, you know? That was gone. I'm
now 100
60-some pounds. So, I had to
redefine myself and find
my meaning in life and come back a
different person, you know? It teaches
you how to value the small things. Just
being able to go outside and walk my
dog. It made me really start
prioritizing
what's really important in life.
And it bring me and my family closer.
It bring it got my spiritual life with
God closer. So, it was a learning
lesson. But uh
I still love the industry.
I'm still recovering now.
I'm still not 100%.
I'm in a much better place than I was
when I first got out the hospital,
obviously. Um I've been able to gain
weight. Y'all can see I got a little
something now. Don't hate. Hey. Hey. So,
I still have one more surgery that's
coming up. It's supposed to be it could
be up to a 10-hour surgery. Um and then
I'll be able to, you know,
get back to the most normal version of
myself that that I can be. So,
recovery's been uh rough. I started
getting questions cuz you know, um
when you're a public figure,
some people really don't care about what
you're going through. And I was starting
getting, "Man, when you coming back?
When you doing this? When you doing
that?" And I would start to think like,
"Am I going to get back in this? Like,
how does my family feel about me getting
back in this?" I love it. I miss it. So,
what I did was I had a test run.
And this was going to be my determining
factor if I would get back into this.
Um I went out on a hunt.
And I told myself if I'm one step
behind,
if I'm
feeling scared or if I hesitate,
I'm done.
Cuz that split second I get killed or
someone else killed.
And literally when I got out there, I'm
like 160. I'm still frail. I
shouldn't even been out there, to be
honest, but I had to see how I felt. I
didn't skip a beat.
It still felt good. I wasn't scared. I
still got the same rush. I still felt
the same way.
I said, "It's not It's not time for me
to leave yet. If I need to go out,
I will go out." But I'm not just out
there like I was before. And then me
start
sharpening different tools within this
business, my managing.
You know what I mean? You know, I plan
on opening up shop here in the metro
area, Detroit, Toledo. So, I'm just
sharpening different areas of myself and
not just be focused on that part.
I 100% think there should be more
training
and better screening. No different from
being a law, you know, a police officer.
Um but we don't necessarily have the
same
processes they do. So, I would say more
training
on the mental part of it. You know, I
get so many guys that call me, "Hey, uh
Tank. Yeah, I'm I'm I want to be I want
to come along, man. I got I got my CCW."
If that's the first thing you tell me
that you got your gun license,
I'm turned off.
Immediately, because that's that's all
you thinking about right away
is guns and and toting a gun. I've never
had to shoot at any at anyone.
I've had physical altercations with
people. I'm always
leveled, and I talk very calmly. It's
definitely a dying business, at least in
Ohio. And I know that it's like that in
other in other states, as well. Um it's
just
you know, with with all the the
political people trying to push cash
bail away, you know,
it's making it harder. So, some people
would rather just go a different route
than than take a risk. It is hard to
arrest someone that is high on drugs.
I've had several crazy arrests where
they didn't feel anything. It was like
arresting the Hulk. Sometimes it's not
worth
the little bit of money you're getting,
you know? I think that the future could
be great if we start getting
more individuals
to get in this for the right reasons
and not for the wrong reasons.
Obviously, the the the community the
communities that have um
you know, lesser financial stability,
they're going to be affected by this
more versus someone who has the money,
they can just get straight out. And it's
unfair, you know? Everyone deserves
freedom, and everyone deserves to be
able to get bailed out of jail,
regardless of your financial
um you know, status.
>> Has ICE affected how bounty hunters
operate?
>> ICE has affected
us personally is now
when someone calls me to get out of jail
just not a US citizen or they're just
over here on a visa or something, we
can't take the chance of getting them
out. Versus before all this was
happening, we would get them out, but
now
we get them out, it's a chance ICE is
going to come get them and now they're
gone. But I haven't even personally seen
any ICE agents. I guess they just
deployed them to Cleveland, so once I
catch this flight back home, I guess
I'll see them at the airport.
So, when I was in college
I was uh thinking about
what's next? And I went to school for
nursing. I have a BSN. When I seen the
football wasn't going to go, you know,
to the next level
then I started looking at well, what can
I do where I can still be athletic, I
can still be outside, and um I started
looking into being a US Marshal. There
was a government shutdown for a while at
this time. So, that was off the board.
So, I started doing more
research and I was like, what's this
bounty hunting stuff? I'm like, wow,
it's
it's kind of similar, but it's
it's different. Like, I don't have to
cut my my hair off, my facial I'm like,
shoot, I can wear regular clothes. So,
when I moved back to Ohio, I moved back
for my daughter
I was doing like dead end jobs, like
cleaning malls and just jobs like that,
but I was also bounty hunting because
I wanted to
pursue this career and be great at it,
and I felt something I could be
successful at it. So, what I would do is
go and contact every single bondsman
that would give me a chance, and
none of them would give me a chance.
Except one. There was one bondsman
rest in peace, he was a good guy, good
man, his name was John Craven.
Um very big bondsman, had a lot of
agents, and uh he took a chance on me.
Well, I just took a chance. He like,
yeah, I got some guys. I don't know I
can't find them here. And I found the
guy in 2 days.
And he was like, oh, okay. So, he gave
me another case.
Found him. Few days. Kept giving me
cases. Now he's like,
this guy is good. Now he's giving me
cases
from his other agents. Now different
companies are starting to hit me up. So,
he opened up doors for me. And then it
was it was uphill from there.
So, I had great relationships with
certain bondsmen
um that I just kept working for. I
decided to become a bondsman at Slide
Bail Bonds. Tony Sylvester, that's
that's my brother. He told me he was
like, you're going to get tired of
hunting at some point. He was like,
you're going to want to start a family.
You're going to want more consistent
money. He was like, you need to get into
the bonds.
And I was like, all right. I'll try this
out. It's been curtains ever since. And
he was right. It's more consistent.
Um you will get tired of hunting and
being gone for days.
And it's it's it's it's job security. If
you are
advertised right and you you know,
you're in the right place, you know, you
you're getting calls every day to get
people out. So, you can be home more.
You can
uh have a family. So, um yeah, he got me
into
the actual bail bondsman space. Because
I do hunt, um
I'm able to just go get them myself.
They kind of go hand in hand, but if you
can write bonds and hunt your people,
you're in a good position. I started
filming um literally on the hunt in
Daytona Beach with a flip phone. And I
started seeing people react to it like,
oh, this is cool. I like this guy. He
different. And I just kept going with
it. Um the more successful, the more
money I would get, I would invest it
back into the production. So, then I
went from a flip phone to a iPhone. Then
I went to a camera. Then I just kept
elevating the more I would be successful
in dumping it in
um into the production until you know, I
got something solid. I also wanted to
give
a different perception of a person with
a badge. I wanted kids to see
a young black man with a badge on just
doing good, and you can go this lane.
You can be successful, and I wanted to
to them to associate a face with a badge
and not have ill will, and just show
that you can do anything that you put
your mind to it, no matter how crazy it
is, or how crazy people think it is.
It's okay to do things are outside the
norm. You can find me on YouTube at
Bounty Tank. Working on my documentary
and my album is coming out. It is a
testimony
of my life and addictions and and
and strongholds that I had to break it
and just showing the process
of me rehabbing and just the whole
entire process of making this
this album.
>> Hi, I'm a producer and authorized
account. If you enjoyed this video, then
please subscribe and comment with more
topics that you'd like us to cover in
this series.